Contact

hrudaipabbisetty@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/hruday-pabbisetty-b46991113 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

C++

С

Number Theory

Certifications

Codechef Certified Data Structure & Algorithms Programme (CCDSAP) (Advanced Level)

Codechef Certified Data Structure & Algorithms programme (CCDSAP) (Foundation Level)

hruday pabbisetty

Software Engineer at Microsoft

Hyderabad

Summary

Experienced Curator with a demonstrated history of working in the computer software industry. Skilled in C++, Data Structures, Algorithms. Strong arts and design professional with a Bachelor of Technology - BTech focused in Electrical Engineering from National Institute of Technology Rourkela.

Experience

Microsoft Software Engineer June 2019 - Present (1 year 3 months) Hyderabad Area, India

CodeChef

Problem Curator
July 2017 - Present (3 years 2 months)

I designed few questions which were used in Codechef Long challenges.

Amazon

Software Development Engineering Internship May 2018 - July 2018 (3 months) Bangalore

Worked as a Software Development Engineering Intern at Amazon Development Center India Pvt Ltd.

Education

National Institute of Technology Rourkela

Bachelor of Technology - BTech, Electrical Engineering · (2015 - 2019)